So here, in my opinion, are three ways to determine if the source you're getting your information from is actually providing comprehensive analysis that can be genuinely helpful to you in these times.
One, are they still talking about Democrats versus Republicans?
Now, I'm not saying that there isn't conversations that need to be had around how these two parties are behaving.
However, to only be talking about these two parties and to still be talking about them as adversarial, as if there is not a shared link between them, is wholly unintellectual and simply just lying.
I feel like the only true analysis to be had about these parties right now is the ways in which they operate dysfunctionally for the actual populace.
So if your analysis is still leaning into I'm a Democrat, mm-mm.
Two, do you have a geopolitical context?
For instance, if their North Star and the center of their orbit is the United States, then that means that they're not thinking geopolitically because that is simply not the center of the world for everybody else.
If their North Star is Donald Trump, whether they like him or not, then they're basing the way that they are actually doing analysis of the world on Donald Trump.
Case in point, praising the person who won the Nobel Peace Prize simply because it meant Donald Trump didn't win.
Not acknowledging that this person is a very loud Zionist, a huge supporter of Donald Trump, and is actually very against any level of socialism that is taking place in Venezuela and wants a war.
Third, is their analysis centered on identity politics?
So if you're watching folks who are solely talking about being American or being Jewish or being black or being white or conservative, etc.,
then it's honestly impossible for them to be giving a thorough, comprehensive look at what's going on to provide you information from that same perspective.
It's not to say that they don't lean from a particular lens because, I mean, that's just kind of natural as beings that we see from where we see from.
But to be giving you news only from that space means they're only keeping you in that space.
And I will promise you there is much more space to take up.
And the bonus is that if they're not addressing Israel, then they're either bought or scared, either of which is not helpful to you.
It's really important in these times to really, if you want to be in the know, to actually be in the know from sources that actually are able to kind of wrangle all the things that are happening at all the times, which at this point is a lot.